<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
    Document   : osnews.rss.xml.xml
    Created on : July 13, 2013, 12:11 PM
    Author     : cp
    Description:
        Purpose of the document follows.
-->

<rss xmlns:osnews="http://osnews.com/rss2#" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>OSNews</title>
        <link>http://www.osnews.com</link>
        <description>Exploring the Future of Computing</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2001-2013, David Adams</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 09:54:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.osnews.com/images/osnews.gif</url>
            <title>OSNews.com</title>
            <link>http://www.osnews.com</link>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Microsoft details new WP8 update, but real fixes won't come until 2014</title>
            <link>http://osnews.com/story/27186/Microsoft_details_new_WP8_update_but_real_fixes_won_t_come_until_2014</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://osnews.com/story/27186/Microsoft_details_new_WP8_update_but_real_fixes_won_t_come_until_2014</guid>
            <description>The general gist? A minor update somewhere this year, but the real update won't come until 2014. In the meantime, we'll have to... 
            "Resuming..." ...settle for CardDAV/CalDAV support, some additional HTML5 support, and fixes for Xbox Music metadata. We were promised regular updates and 
            an early access program for enthusiasts - but Microsoft failed to deliver, once more. For all intents and purposes, thanks... "Resuming..." ...to the switch 
            to the Windows NT kernel, the Windows Phone we're using today has very little additional functionality to offer over what we were using on WP7 release day. 
            I've been a Windows Phone user since WP7 release day, but Microsoft has lost me.
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 12:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
            <author>donotreply@osnews.com (Thom Holwerda)</author>
            <category>Windows</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The OPPO Find 5 - Nexus but not from Google</title>
            <link>http://osnews.com/story/27185/The_OPPO_Find_5_-_Nexus_but_not_from_Google</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://osnews.com/story/27185/The_OPPO_Find_5_-_Nexus_but_not_from_Google</guid>
            <description>I was in the running for a new Android phone, and I was quite dead set on getting a Nexus 4 - however, there was another phone in the 
            running: the OPPO Find 5, a smrtphone with lots of positive reviews, but from a small manufacturer. The point that made me choose the Find 5 over 
            the Nexus 4? OPPO actively supports the ROM community by giving away free phones, and boasts support for CyanogenMod, Paranoid Android, and an AOSP ROM, 
            and obviously, rooting is easy. OPPO also updates its own firmware/ROM twice per month with new features, which is a far cry from the big boys. If 
            you're looking for a new Android phone, you might want to consider looking beyond the established players as well, and support a company who works 
            closely with the community - something the big player still need to learn properly. Once the device arrives on my doorstep, I'll be sure to tell you 
            all about it, and if it lives up to the hype. It is, after all, from a relatively unknown company, so I am taking a risk here. I am a little bit nervous. 
            But hey, if none of us takes the risk, we'll be stuck with the big players forever.
            </description>            
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 11:14:05 GMT</pubDate>
            <author>donotreply@osnews.com (Thom Holwerda)</author>
            <category>PDAs, Cellphones, Wireless</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>